Hey, babe, aren't you excited
we're going on our honeymoon?
Yeah, I am.
♪ Bermuda, Bahamas,
come on, pretty mama. ♪
That's right, get
it out your system
while we're alone.
Hey.
We came to say good-bye.
Yeah, have
a great honeymoon.
Thanks.
I better go pack.
Oh, no, I already packed.
The only thing I couldn't find
though was your Speedo.
Speedo?
I don't have a Speedo.
I'm going to go pack my
regular long bathing suit.
Oh, good, you're still here.
I wanted to tell you
to have a good honeymoon.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, and I also wanted
you guys to know
that I am telling
the father today.
What, what, what?
We know it's Ross.
How? How do you know?
It was his sweater.
But, oh, my God!
Wow, I so wanted
Ross to know first
but I am so relieved
that you guys know.
That's so great
and I'm going to be
your baby's aunt.
I know.
Me, too.
I'm going to be an uncle.
Come here.
You're all going to be
aunts and uncles.
Yeah, but I'm the only
one related by blood.
Okay, great.
So now that you guys all know
you can help me,
give me some advice
on how I'm going to tell Ross.
Well, what were you
going to say?
Well, I was going to tell him
I'm going to have the baby
and he can be as involved
as he wants.
Well, that
sounds good.
Yeah, but, you know,
how do I start?
I mean, what's the first thing
that I say?
Okay, great. Thanks.
Hey, good luck.
Yeah, bye.
Hey, what was that all about?
Well, I guess there's
no harm in telling you now.
Rachel and Ross
are going to have a baby.
( high-pitched ):
What?!
I didn't even know that...
Why didn't you tell me?
Why am I talking like this?
I didn't think you
could keep it a secret.
( high-pitched ):
What?!
( normal voice ):
I am an excellent secret keeper.
I have kept all of our secrets.
What secrets?
Oh, no, no, Joey.
I'm not going to tell you
because I am an excellent
secret keeper.
Psst. You tell me later.
You already know.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's DOA ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Oh, it's so romantic
to send people off
on their honeymoon.
You know, Monica and
Chandler are married.
Ross and Rachel
are having a baby.
Maybe you and I
should do something.
All in good time,
my love.
All in good time.
Oh, shoot, I left my guitar
in their apartment.
Well, you can let me
in later, right?
No, I don't have a key.
They took mine
to give to you.
What? They took mine
Why would they
take away our keys?
Maybe they don't trust us.
No, that's not it.
They let me keep my key
the last time they
were out of town.
You mean the time you broke
the ketchup bottle
and cleaned it up with
Monica's guest towels?
Hey, I washed those.
No, you didn't.
Yeah, that didn't
sound like me.
Well, what am I going to do?
I really need my guitar.
Yeah, I have stuff
in there, too.
What stuff?
Monica's chicken parm!
I'll take care of this.
Hey, Mr. Treeger,
it's Joey Tribbiani.
Listen, I need to get into
Monica and Chandler's apartment.
It's an emergency.
Uh, uh, gas leak.
Yeah, oh, and bring
garlic bread.
Hey.
Did Rachel find you?
No, why?
Oh, she was looking for you.
Oh, well, I guess I'll
catch up with her later.
Well, she really wanted
to talk to you now.
Yeah, it seemed
pretty important.
Oh, no.
What?
I think I might know
what this is about.
Really?
Yeah, uh...
We promised we weren't going
to tell anybody this
but, uh...
about a month ago,
Rachel and I slept together.
And?
Wow, I thought you'd be
a little more shocked.
Oh, sorry.
And?
Well, we said
we'd just do it that one time
but now I think she may want
to start things up again.
Yeah, I don't think
that's what it is.
Why, what else could it be?
Oh, wow,
I don't feel well.
No, I'm telling you,
I'm telling you
that's what it is.
No wonder she was looking at
me all funny during the wedding.
She didn't say anything to you?
Maybe it's
something you ate.
Please, just go
and talk to Rachel.
Yeah, I guess I should.
Man... you know
what I have to realize?
Maybe I'm not the type of guy
women can have
just one night with.
You know, they always seem
to want a little bit more.
I should remember that.
Next.
They're kissing,
let's just go around them.
Oh, honey,
leave them alone.
They're in love.
I'm in love, too.
But in an orderly fashion.
Next.
Hi. Can you
do that and walk?
Because she said "next."
Oh.
Sorry.
We didn't hear you.
We're on our honeymoon.
Oh.
Let me see what I can do.
There are some first class
seats available.
Did you hear that?
They bumped them up
to first class
because they're
on their honeymoon.
Come on, let's act like
we're on our honeymoon.
We are on
our honeymoon.
Grab my ass.
Next.
Hi. Sorry.
I almost didn't hear you
because, you know
I'm just so in love
with my new husband.
We're on our honeymoon.
Congratulations.
Thanks.
Mr. Bing
you'll be in 25J
and Mrs. Bing, you're in 25K.
Uh, no, you see,
we're on our honeymoon.
So, um, can you
do your little thing
and bump us up
to first class?
I'm sorry, all the first class
seats are taken.
That couple
got the last two.
You see? If we'd gone
around them like I said
then she would've
given us those tickets.
Damn it.
25J and K.
Any chance those
aren't together?
I still can't believe
they took away my key.
You trust me with yours.
Of course I do.
And I'm going to
get it back to you
just as soon as
they're done with it
at the key shining place.
( banging )
What the hell is that?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Treeger,
what are you doing?
Said there was
a gas leak in here.
Well, why don't you
use your key?
Because by the time
I found it on this thing
the whole place
might have exploded.
If that happens at another
building that I manage
people are going to start
asking questions.
Come on, hurry up.
Oh!
We could've done that.
Look at that,
look at that.
They're going into
the first class lounge.
Do you know what
they have in there?
No.
Me, neither.
We have to get in!
Just act like you belong.
Oh, my God, oranges!
Shh!
Nice to see you again.
Uh, sir.
May I see
your tickets, please?
Yes, of course.
I'm sorry,
would you move your thumb?
I can't see the seat number.
Oh, that's all right,
I have it memorized. It's 1A.
Sir, this is not
a first class ticket.
I'm sorry.
Apology accepted.
Excuse us.
Sir, I'm afraid
I'm going to have
to ask you to leave.
Fine.
Go! Go! Go!
Hi.
Um...
I think there's something that
we really need to talk about.
I think we do.
Why don't we go inside?
Okay.
Look, uh...
I know why you're here.
You do?
Yeah.
And to save you from
any embarrassment
I think maybe
I should talk first.
Okay.
Okay?
Ross and Rachel...
Rachel and Ross...
That's been one heck
of a seesaw, hasn't it?
What?
I mean, look, that...
that one night
we had was fun
and certainly passionate.
But don't you think it's better
if we just stay friends?
Seriously, what?
Okay, okay.
You know what?
If you want to...
we can do it one more time.
I mean, I'd be okay
with that.
In fact, I have
some time right now.
Okay, Ross.
You know what?
Can I talk now?
Oh, sure.
I'm pregnant.
Ross?
Okay.
Whenever you're ready.
And you're the father,
by the way, but you go.
Can I get you some water?
No, I'm good, I'm good.
Ross, there is no
pressure on you, okay?
I mean, you can be
as involved as you want.
Yeah, I, uh...
I'm just, I don't know.
I don't understand...
um... how this happened.
We-we used a condom.
I know, I know
but, you know,
condoms only work
like, 97% of the time.
Wh-what?
What?!
Well, they should
put that on the box!
They do.
No, they don't!
Well, they should put it
in huge block letters!
Okay, Ross, come on.
Let's forget about the condoms.
Oh, well, I may as well have!
Listen, you know what?
I was really freaked out, too,
when I found out...
Freaked out, hey,
I'm not freaked out.
I'm indignant as a consumer.
You know what, let's talk later.
No, no, I want
to talk now, okay?
In fact, I want to talk
to the president
of the condom company.
Okay, you know what?
Maybe I should come back.
Shh!
Okay.
Yeah, I'll press one!
I looked everywhere.
There's no gas leak.
Huh. So, then
I can heat this up?
Anyway, I'll get moving
on that new door.
Oh, great, and listen,
could you do us a favor
and not tell Chandler and Monica
about this
'cause, you know, they don't...
they don't have any kids
of their own
and this door was...
like a child to them.
Well, I'm going to have
to put on a new lock.
They'll find out anyway.
Oh, no.
This looks like
an all-day job.
I'm going to have to cancel
my yoga class.
Hey, Ross.
Hey.
Would you tell Jasmine I can't
make it to yoga class today?
Sure.
Namaste.
Oh, my God,
what happened to the door?
So it's noticeable, huh?
Look, is Rachel here?
I really need to talk to her.
Didn't you two
already talk?
Yeah, but...
Okay, okay, look--
you guys know
that Rachel and I
slept together
but there's
something else.
Rachel's pregnant.
Holy mother of God!
Oh, my God,
can't believe it!
With my child.
That is brand-new
information!
You already know, don't you?
Little bit.
How you doing?
Okay, okay.
I mean, I'll be okay.
It's just, I don't think
I handled it very well.
Well, what'd
you say to her?
Nothing.
But the complaint department
at the condom company
got an earful.
And then, when I turned around,
she was gone.
Oh, Ross.
But, hey, in my defense,
I just found out
that condoms are only, like,
97% effective.
What?
I got to go find her.
Whoa, hey, hold on!
Are you serious?
So, like,
three percent of the time
they don't even work?
Huh? They should put that
on the box!
Evidently, they do.
What?
I can't believe
we're here.
Oh, you got to be kidding me.
What?
( gasps )
As a wedding gift to you,
the hotel would like
to give you
the honeymoon suite.
No, you have been
screwing us all day!
Who are you?
We're you,
just ten seconds later!
You already got the first class
tickets. You got the lounge.
I mean, we should
get free stuff, too!
I mean, you're not
the only ones on
your honeymoon!
Well, you can have
the suite if you want.
We don't care about
where we stay.
We're here to celebrate
our love for each other.
We don't have
to get free stuff.
We just want
to be together.
We need the stuff.
Hey, Monica, it's Joey.
Listen, Phoebe and I
smell gas coming
from your apartment.
What, are you serious?
Joey smells gas.
What else is new?
Yeah, and we'd go check it out,
but you took away our keys.
Well, do something.
Get in there!
How?
I guess I could
break down your door.
Yeah, do that!
And you won't blame us
for any damage?
No!
Are you doing it? I don't
hear anything, come on!
Uh, okay, I'll break it down.
Okay, hi,
he's doing it.
He's breaking down the door.
Okay, we're in.
Okay, Rachel,
you comfortable?
If I said I was,
would you judge me?
The doctor will
be here in a minute
to do your sonogram.
Okay.
( sighs )
Oh, man, I swear
if they sold these
at Pottery Barn...
Hi.
We need to talk.
R-right now?
'Cause I kind of got
an alfresco situation
going on over here.
Please, please, I really...
I want to apologize
for the way I acted
earlier today.
Okay, Ross, that's fine,
but can you please
stay up near my head?
What, oh, yeah, sorry.
I mean, I think I went
a little crazy.
I was thinking about myself
when I really, I should have
been thinking about you.
Head, Ross,
head, Ross, head, Ross.
Right. I just--
I want you to know
that I'm going to be there
through this whole
thing, okay, okay?
The doctor's appointments
the Lamaze classes,
baby-proofing the apartment--
although we could
probably worry about that
till after we get married.
Married?
Well, yeah.
I think we should get married.
What, because that's your answer
to everything?
No, because that's
the right thing to do.
Yeah, maybe, if you're in love.
But Ross,
we are not in love, are we?
No, but...
But still, I mean, you
can't possibly do this alone.
Excuse me?
Come on, Rach.
I mean, you can't even
eat alone in a restaurant.
What?
I'm just saying,
if you can't eat by yourself
how do you expect
to have a baby by yourself?
I can too eat by myself.
When have you ever?
When certain people
leave the table
and I am not finished.
Well, certain other people
take two hours
to eat a bowl of soup.
Oh, please,
you inhale your food.
I grew up with Monica.
If you didn't eat fast,
you didn't eat!
( knocking )
Am I interrupting?
Oh, no, Dr. Long.
Please come in.
This is Ross. He is the father.
But not the husband
because evidently,
she can do this alone.
Oh, nice to meet you.
I'll get started on this.
I don't know why you can't admit
that you need me.
I do need you--
I need you to stay near my head!
Okay, everything looks good.
Here it is on the screen.
There's your uterus
and right here...
is your baby.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
There it is, I see it.
Congratulations.
I'll give you two a minute.
Thank you.
Pretty amazing, huh?
I don't see it!
( crying )
What? What?
I can't see it!
You-you just said
that you did.
I know. I lied.
I didn't want her to think
I was a terrible mother.
I can't even see my own baby!
Oh, sure, come here.
Sure you can.
Come here, look.
It-it's right there.
Oh.
Oh, it's beautiful.
I see it now.
Do you really?
No, I don't see it!
Okay, come on, come on.
Okay, okay, you see
this-this tiny thing
that looks like a peanut?
Yeah.
Sweetie, that's it.
That's it?
Well, I saw that!
( giggles )
Oh, thank you.
You're welcome.
Wow.
I can't believe
that's our baby.
Yeah, that's our baby.
Hi.
Hey.
So, how was the doctor?
Oh, everything went great.
Oh, good.
Oh, hey,
show them
the picture of your uterus.
Aw.
I don't see the baby.
Where is it?
Oh, no, I know.
I couldn't see it
either at first
but it's right, um...
Ross, I lost it again.
Oh...